ronherman.com 2014-02-10

# Shop Womens & Mens Clothes and Accessories Online from L.A.'s Ron Herman Boutique (www.RonHerman.com)

**Privacy Policy**

At Ron Herman, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, which is why we do not sell, rent, or loan any personal identifiable information regarding our customers to any third party. We hope the policy below will answer all of your questions regarding how we treat information gathered from visitors to Ron Herman. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us by sending an email to **_[Customer Service](mailto:CustomerService@RonHerman.com)_** __. 

**Information Collection and Use**

Ron Herman collects personally identifiable information when you request information from Ron Herman. On such occasions, Ron Herman asks for your name, email address, zip code and personal information concerning your interests, occupation, gender and other demographic information. Ron Herman also receives and records information from server logs from your browser including cookie information relation to pages requested and the like. This helps us better understand what our customers would like to see from us. We use this information internally regarding what our customers want and mailing of circulars and special offers from Ron Herman. We do not give or sell Personal Information to any other party. If at any time you do not want to receive offers and/or circulars from us. You can always remove yourself from our mailing list by sending an e-mail to **_[Customer Service](mailto:CustomerService@RonHerman.com)_** __

**Protecting Children**

Ron Herman is committed to protecting the privacy of children. Ron Herman recommends that children under the age of 13 obtain the consent of their parent or guardian before submitting any information to Ron Herman. 

**Opt-out Email policy**

We ask that you tell us when you do not wish to receive periodic emails from us. We will only send email for customer service purposes and to those visitors who have indicated that they wish to receive other types of email from us. If at any time you wish to stop receiving email from us, you can always remove your name from our mailing list by sending an email to **_[Customer Service](mailto:CustomerService@RonHerman.com)_** __ stating that you wish to unsubscribe. 

**Use of Cookies**

Ron Herman uses cookies to enhance the interactive nature of your Internet experience and to provide a convenient feature to save you time. Cookies enable Ron Herman to quickly retrieve specific information from previous visits and to recall features that you may have customized on your browser. 

**Scope of Policy**

This policy applies to Ron Herman’s treatment of personally identifiable information that Ron Herman collects through Ron Herman’s site and when you use Ron Herman’s services. This policy does not apply to practices of companies whose sites may be linked to Ron Herman. For access to the privacy policies of such linked sites please refer to the information provided by such sites at their home pages. Also see below under the heading “Hypertext Links”. 

**Security of the Information You Provide**

Among our top priorities is keeping your Personal Information secure. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which provides the highest level of security currently available for secure transactions, to encrypt all of your Personal Information before it is transmitted to us. Encrypted information cannot be read or recorded as it travels over the Internet. You can tell you are sending information securely by the unbroken key icon or closed lock icon that should appear at the bottom of your internet browser’s window (depending on what browser you use). These icons will appear when you are placing an order on our Web site. In addition, you will see our site address change slightly, from http: to https: indicating a secure server connection is being used. 

Additionally, access to your Personal Information is provided only to our employees and agents who have a need to know such information for the purpose of fulfilling your order and offering our high level of customer service. The computers that store your Personal Information are located in a separate facility which employs the latest in firewall and security technology. 

**Modifications to this Policy**

Ron Herman may make modifications or amendments to this policy from time to time. In the event that such changes alter how Ron Herman gathers, processes, uses or discloses your personally identifiable information, Ron Herman will post such changes on our site. 

**Intellectual Property**

Ron Herman, its suppliers, licensors, or the original creators of all materials on the Ron Herman Web site own all copyrightable subject matter on this Web site and all trademarks, patents, proprietary information, technologies, products, processes or other proprietary rights of Ron Herman and/or such other parties. No license to or right in any such copyrights, trademarks, patents, proprietary information, technologies, products processes and other proprietary rights of Ron Herman and/or other parties is granted to or conferred upon you. In addition, direct linking, deep linking, framing, page-jacking, metatagging, and using a robot, spider, or automated device of any kind to monitor or copy our Web site is strictly prohibited. 

Not with standing the foregoing, Ron Herman hereby authorizes you only to copy the content herein solely for your personal and private use in learning about, evaluating, or acquiring Ron Herman products. Except where expressly noted, no other permission is granted to print, copy, reproduce, distribute, transmit, upload, download, store, display in public, alter, or modify the content contained on this site. Any unauthorized use of any material contained on this site may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and communications regulations and statutes. Any other use of materials on this site, including reproduction for purposes other than those expressly permitted above, modification, distribution, or republication, without prior written permission of Ron Herman is strictly prohibited. Any copy made by you as permitted above must retain all copyright and trademark notices, including any other proprietary notices, contained in the materials. The use of such materials on any other Web site or in any environment of networked computers is prohibited. 

**Hypertext Links**

In the event, this site contains hypertext links to sites that are not created or maintained by Ron Herman, this Privacy Policy applies only to this Web site and not to any of these third party Web sites. Ron Herman is not responsible for the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, or completeness of those third party sites. The inclusion of any link to such sites does not imply endorsement, sponsorship, or recommendation by Ron Herman of the site. Ron Herman disclaims any liability for links (1) from another Web site to www.Ron Herman and (2) to another Web site from ronherman.virid.com cannot guarantee the standards of any Web site to which links are provided on this site nor shall Ron Herman be held responsible for the contents of non-Ron Herman sites, or any subsequent links. For this reason, Ron Herman does not represent or warrant that the contents of any third party Web site is accurate, compliant with state or federal law, or compliant with copyright or other intellectual property laws. Ron Herman does not endorse the contents of these third party Web sites in any way. Also, Ron Herman is not responsible for web casting or any other form of transmission received from any linked Web site. Any reliance on the contents of a third party Web site is done at your own risk and you assume all responsibilities and consequences resulting from such reliance.

 **Your Acceptance of these Terms**

By using our Web site, you agree to accept the Ron Herman privacy policy. Make sure you read this policy carefully, because if you do choose to use our Web site, you automatically agree to this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Web site.
